<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Women Safety App</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="contact">Contact</string>

    <string name="openNavDrawer"> Navigation Drawer Open</string>
    <string name="closeNavDrawer"> Navigation Drawer Closed</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="ForgotPassword"> Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="NOT"> Not on S-I-D-E-K-I-C-K yet? </string>
    <string name="SignUp">Sign Up! </string>

    <string name="WhatApp"> Help!! I\'m in <b>DANGER</b> \n My current location is http://maps.google.com/?q=19.0410042,73.0168106 </string>

    <string name="help">Please follow the below steps properly:\n\n\n\t1:Register Your Phone Number.\n\t2:Register Your Guardian Numbers.\n\t3:Always maintain working internet \n\t connection.\n\t4:SHAKE your phone vertically 3 times \n\t to ask for "HELP" in case of emergency \n\t to alert your guardians.</string>
    <string name="Privacy_Policy">
       <H4><b>MIT License </b></H4> \n




<H5><b>Copyright (c) 2020 S-I-D-E-K-I-C-K </b></H5> \n\n

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:  \n\n

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all
copies or substantial portions of the Software.  \n\n

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE
SOFTWARE.



    </string>


    <string name="About_App">

 Features of the app- \n\n

1.SOS/Emergency - Send a SMS containing- \"I am In Danger\" to selected 3 contacts and your GPS location to track you with 3 vertical phone swings or just a click of a button. \n
2.Alarm - An alarm (Police Siren) is set up within 5 seconds. It may help to scare the pursuer. \n
3.Fake Call- How often, do we think that if we had an incoming call right now, it can save us from the situation we are in right now. \n
4.Camera - Email the latest Media clicked by your Camera in every 10 minutes to your emergency contacts and save it on your secondary Storage. \n


    </string>

    <string name="App_Detail">
        An Android App for everyone irrespective of any gender discrimination (but especially developed for Women Saftey), which will send SOS/Emergancy message to registered Emergency numbers, based on a specific 3-5 vertical swings. The SOS will be comprised of user\'s current GPS coordinates,personal information and latest media in your storage to those numbers.

Make Sure that "Google" ,"WhatApp","Gmail" App is Installed on your phone and you give this App proper Access Permission like Call, SMS, Microphone, Camera, GPS.
    </string>
</resources>